filedudes.com 2009-03-25

# FileDudes: Privacy Statement for FileDudes.com

FileDudes.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Keeping you informed of our information gathering practices and our policy for how we use that information is important to us at filedudes.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log files**  
The server stores your host, your operating system, your browser, and referring page in the server's log file when you access filedudes.com. This information is stored, by default, by most websites. We do not use this information to track individual users; these log files are analyzed by statistical packages to determine trends in visitor patterns, such as which pages are most popular and which referrers send the most visitors. Your host name is used only to determine statistics about the site's percentages of traffic from various countries. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not use cookies on this site. Some of our advertisers use cookies on this site. But We have no access to or control over these cookies. They use cookies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. FileDudes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. FileDudes.com is not liable for the content of other websites available through hyperlinks from this Site (hereinafter "Linked Sites"). Such Linked Sites have been created by third parties. FileDudes.com does not endorse the Linked Sites. Your navigation to these Linked Sites and their marking as bookmarks are your sole responsibility. FileDudes.com may refuse the use of hyperlinks to this Site if the link is made to another page than the home page of this Site, through deep linking, framing or mirroring, or if the surrounding context in which the hyperlink is used is harmful to the honor, reputation or commercial interest of FileDudes.com.

**About Listed Software**  
All software products are submitted by the author, if specific software violates the copyright, please contact us and we will remove it as soon as possible.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
